{
    "1": {
      "question":"How many clubs are in the Ghana premier league?",
      "answers": "20:18:12",
      "correct_answer": "20"
    },
    "2": {
      "question":"How many clubs are in the English  premier league?",
      "answers": "19:21:20",
      "correct_answer": "19"
    },
    "3": {
      "question":"How many clubs are in the  Bundesliga league?",
      "answers": "18:17:19",
      "correct_answer": "18"
    },
    "4": {
      "question":"How many clubs are in the Spanish Laliga  league?",
      "answers": "20:18:16",
      "correct_answer":"20"
    },
    "5":{
      "question":"Which country is Lionel Messi from ?",
      "answers":"Spain:Argentina:Italy",
      "correct_answer": "Argentina"
    },
    "6": {
      "question":"How many UEFA menâ€™s best player awards has Messi won?",
      "answers": "2:5:6",
      "correct_answer":"2"
    },
    "7": {
      "question":"How many counties has Messi played in?",
      "answers":"4:5:6",
      "correct_answer":"4"
    },
    "8":{
      "question":"What is the name of Germany's senior  national team coach?",
      "answers":"Julian Nagelsmann:Joachim Low:Solomon Adei",
      "correct_answer":"Julian Nagelsmann"
    },
    "9":{
      "question":"What is the name of the Ghana senior national team captain?",
      "answers":"Asamoah Gyan:Andre Ayew:Wisdom Dzeagu",
      "correct_answer":"Andre Ayew"
    },
    "10":{
      "question":"Which club does Ronaldo currently play for?",
      "answers":"Juventus:Al-Nassr:Manchester United",
      "correct_answer":"Al-Nassr"
    },
    "11":{
      "question":"Who is the most capped plaeyr in the world?",
      "answers":"Ramos:Ronaldo:Messi",
      "correct_answer":"Ronaldo"
    },
    "12":{
      "question":"Who is the highest payed player in the world?",
      "answers":"Neymar:Ronaldo:Messi",
      "correct_answer":"Ronaldo"
    },
    "13":{
      "question":"which club does Mohammed Kudus play for?",
      "answers":"Ajax:Right to dream:West ham United",
      "correct_answer":"West ham United"
    },
    "14":{
      "question":"which country is Jude Bellingham from?",
      "answers":"Spain:England:America",
      "correct_answer":"England"
    },
    "15":{
      "question":"Richest football club in the world is?",
      "answers":"Real Madrid: Manchester City:Liverpool",
      "correct_answer":",Manchester City"
    }
    
  }
